(804) 929-7374 I taylorradtke@gmail.com I www.taylorradtke.com I Alexandria, VA

#### SKILLS

#### W3C Validated HTML5

#### BEM/CSS3 via Sass

Bourbon / Neat Foundation Skeleton Bootstrap

## JavaScript, ES6

Ember jQuery Babel React Gatsby Node.js

Vue

#### PHP, Wordpress

Theme Development Advanced Custom Fields Admin/Plugin Setup SQL Management **Custom Functionality** Inheritance Model

# Web Design

UI/UX Design Sketching Interaction Design Grid & Layout Wireframing Color Theory Rapid Prototyping Typography Usability Graphic Design

## **EDUCATION**

#### **2015 - PRESENT**

## General Assembly

Front-End Development Alexandria, VA

#### 2011 - 2014

# Virginia Commonwealth University

Information Systems Alexandria, VA

#### 2009 - 2011

#### J. Sargeant Reynolds

Business (A.A.S) Richmond, VA

#### ABOUT ME

Taylor Radtke is a creative mind who specializes in minimal design that displays a bold message. After three plus years of marketing in the service industry, Taylor takes his social skills mastered from constructing cocktails through college to create a finished project that his client truly loves. Taylor has a great latitude of culture due to his upbringing in Southern California, before transitioning to the mid-Atlantic region to further his career and education. He is passionate about web-design as a functional piece of art, and strive to let his mind continue to peruse the beauty of the digital experience.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### JULY 2017 - PRESENT

## Cisco Engineer Herndon, VA

Created a completely dynamic Wordpress Theme used by hundreds of different partners that brands all pages and components with their personal branding (Typography, brand colors, logo, etc)

#### OCT 2016 – JULY 2017

#### AAPA

Full-Stack Web Developer Alexandria, VA

Completely redesigned website in under 4 months, on a new CMS. Developed web site mock-ups for clients to ensure quality control and client satisfaction before project development phase. Lead Designer and Developer for Annual Conference Site.

#### APR 2016 - OCT 2016

## The Motley Fool Front-End Web Developer (Contractor)

Alexandria, VA

Bethesda, MD

Cisco - 2018

Developed and designed microsites, newsletters. Developed and designed, and e-mail templates. Conducted BrowserStack usability testing for pages on all devices.

Responsible for designing and maintaining web banners in various

#### NOV 2015 - APR 2016

## Total Wine & More Digital Media Designer (Contractor)

formats to be displayed on any device. Conducted analyses using Google Analytics and Google AdWords.

## AWARDS / CERTIFICATIONS

## Green Belt Security Certified Cisco - 2018

# White Belt Security Certified

Spot Award, 50th Landing Page

AAPA - 2017